Hello everybody.
Finally we have come this far where we are going to bill the Add To Cart feature so that our using and
add products to the cart we need to structure the Schimmel speech first before anything so I have uploaded
file and lecture and I want to download a file and copy the content so I'm going to open it up and I'm
going to open a file and you want to copy this entire file and open up your client folder and open Page's
folder and create a new file and give it a name card and not view and what a piece is here.
Saved it.
And let's go back to a chrome and let's visit local those 9000 cart and see the content.
There we have it.
This is his shopping cart page.
It is the same as Amazon's one.
And if you see this recently viewed items this would be dummy data for the time being.
But this will be related to browsing history later on.
So in this section we are going to focus on building this entire Add To Cart feature.
So I'll see you guys in the next video.