What is view X view X is a state management.
When we have a single source of truth it is easier for all of the components to use.
For example we implemented the logging beach when we were logging.
We mutated the off state from logging falls to log true and if you realize we actually use the off state
user ID components like review beach nav bar and finally you use it in profile.
He made our life easier when we have view X but only use view X if many of the components required to
use it to aspirin for.
Off object.
I would never bars like these.
Hello.
And then the user name and even the address of the user.
We need to access the off object right.
So it is easier if we can put it in one single source of truth and we can just communicate with that
data like even review page we need the object as well.
And even profile we need to off object as well.
Why do we have to replicate it in every single page or every single component.
While we can put it in one single source of truth.
Just thing of state as giant big javascript object wherever you put it in the state.
It will go to log off and after this we're going to have cart.
So that is actually what is view x is just a giant javascript object.
So for our art to cut feature to our components and pages that will need to access to car object.
So we need to put a cart object in our state so as you can see first we have cart on the nav bar that
requires to communicate with the car object and then we have a another picture.
We're going to create a future where you can review your order you can check like estimated delivery
and b load estimate delivery will be the cart content.
So we need to communicate with the car object as well.
And then when we click Add to cart it has to communicate with the car object as well to increase the
number of products in the cart.
And finally we have the obviously the cart page which we just created in pass video where this will
be all of your products in the cart.
As you can see there are a lot of pages in components that need to communicate with the car objects.
Hence why we need to put this car object in a view x so that all the components or pages can communicate
with that object.
So this is the diagram of what is view X. There's actions mutations date and view components.
So let's go through one by one.
So actions are when you click a button like when you update or add a product that is considered an action
an axis mutation.
Mutations are when you want to change the state.
So in this case when you click a button it will increase the cart Lane from zero to 10.
Depends on how many products you add to the cart.
So there is a mutation.
We mutate the cart Lane.
So let me put it in a sentence when you click a button it will mutate the state and the view component
will re render the newly updated state.
Simple as that.
So here is add to cart and then this is the view X single source of truth as you can see there are states
like of cart and product quantity and then there are methods which you can add to cart.
It's not supposed to be methods supposed to be actions.
It's the same thing.
And as you can see this is the view x is just a huge javascript object.
Is off car and product quantity will be state actually method is actions to be honest.
We have a touch of you X when dealing with education.
We started off user object in a state.
This is off now and once we actually log in it will change to object and then as log and true strategy
and in the user object in the next few days we will implement our view x.
So we're going to create a state and then we're going to create an action.
So I'll see you guys in the next video.