Since we already learn about view X now it is time to implement it.
So let's go to our index dot J S under store folder which is the view x file and then we want to create
export cons state and this would be all of us state.
You're gonna have cart which would be in every cart lane which would be zero.
We want to create actions so export Bond's actions and the name to action that we're going to implement
first is at product to cart and then state.
Kim banana product.
I'll explain to you line by line after this.
So now let's just write a code.
Cut product to state not card not fine.
And then it will be brought down.
I.
Equals to product.
No product then commit push product to court.
So in order for you to create an action you need to pass state and commit state is because we want to
access the state here.
CART AND CART length and then commit gives us the ability to access mutations function.
And if you see this comment this is how we going to access the mutation functions of Iran which we have
to create.
Product is the product that the user will add and the logic is simple.
First we check in our cart state to find whether the product that the user about to ate exists or not
in the cart.
Hence why we are doing equals to product that the user will add and a product in the cart we check does
it exist.
If a product doesn't exist then we want to push it a product to the cart bypassing this product and
user want to.
And this will be sent to our mutation function later on.
Else if the product does exist in the cart we simply just want to increase the quantity of the product
which is another mutation function that we have to create later on.
And if we pass in the product that we want to increase the quantity of.
And finally another mutation function just to increase the length of the cart.
So it is really simple.
We just learn about state and then we learn about action.
So in the next video we will learn on how to implement this tree mutations functions.
You must be wondering why not just do the push to cart in here and increment product cure and as well
as increment cart length here.
Can we just do it in one action.
We can do that but a conventional view access is better to separate when you want to mutate a state
in a separate function which is in mutation and action simply just to navigate which mutation that you
want to use.
So we are actually following the best practice.
So I'll see you guys in the next video where we're going to implement mutations function.