Hello everybody.
In this video we are going to create transmutation function so that we can mutate the cart state so
let's go and do that type export Khan's mutations
and then the first mutation function will be push product cart and then we have to pass in the state
so that we can access to cart state and then the product which will be from this comet and we type product
not quantity it goes to one and then state can't push product this mutation function is pushing the
product to cart for the first time we add an additional key to our product object which is quantity
equals to 1 and then we push the product into the cart state.
Very simple.
That is the logic of push product the cart and then the next mutation function would be incremental
product quantity and then when a passing state and a product as well so in here will be pretty much
the same we will be product not quantity but instead of setting into one because the product already
exists in the cart we do.
Plus plus.
And then let index of product ecosystem cart that index of passing the product then to state that cart
that's place index of product 1 and then product.
This mutation function will update the quantity.
So the product already exists in the cart then we just want to update the quantity and then we have
to update the old product in the cart with the updated version of the product because we increment the
quantity by one to do so we have to search for an index of the product in the cart which is index off
let's see in the cart there are apple orange and mango.
So how do we find the position of orange JavaScript as a function call index of bypassing orange in
here the index of product will be product is one because it is 0 1 index for 0 and index 1.
So we just want to get the position of the product.
So by getting the position or product we have to update the product to all product in the cart.
So let's say we want to update this orange into something different like for example we want to change
it to banana.
So we're passing banana in here we are replacing the object of this position which is orange to banana.
So now once we have run this function it will be
because we have to update our cart product.
If we just incremented quantity then a product in the court will be the same you wont change because
we did not update the product in a car yet.
So hence why we have to do splice to do so.
And a final mutation would be incremental cart length which we have to loop the cart.
So we just passed the state we didn't have to pass the product because we just want to loop de cart
and we do state DOT cart length will be zero.
And then if state DOT cart Lang is graded in 0 9 we do state not cart map but a product should be state
DOT cart length plus product not quantity and we say it simple as that.
So increment court logic is super simple.
Whenever this mutation function runs it will always set the cart to zero it will revert the cart length
of zero then we check if the cart Lang in the actual cart not Lang is greater than zero meaning they
are products in a cut that we want to loop the cart by using Matt function and we add the product quantity
to cart length.
So let's say they are the quantity of the product is three four and five.
So by adding to cart Lang it will be plus three.
And then we price for and final will be plus 5.
So the final result in cart Lang will be tough.
So the goal of this incremental cart Lang is to just accumulate all of the product quantity and make
it equal to the cart length in the next video we will implement the at product to cart action on our
product page.
I'll see you guys in the next few.