In this video we will import our product to car action in our product pitch.
Let's do that.
So go to our product pitch which is idea of you and you want to import the action.
So do import met actions from view X and I know you want to open up method type spread operator map
actions and then type at product to car map actions.
It's a function by view Act and its purpose is to map all the actions in our view x file which is index
or J s two methods.
This triple period is to get all the value in the array.
In our case all the actions but we only have one actions so you will map only one action to the method.
Now we can simply call the AT product cost function in our template so we can just copy this at product
cart and let's find our Add To Cart button you start.
Add to cart which is this part and you want to add it here click it goes to add to cart and then you
want to supply a product in here so that it will push the product to the cart state save us because
if you go to index or G S we supply the product in here.
So this is the product we're going to get from this specific parameter and I think we are ready to test
it out.
So let's go to our Chrome.
You want to go to the main page and click any of the products and open up your def to the view dev tools
opening up and you want a change to your state and then you want to click this green color button so
you can see changes in the state.
So now let's try to click Add to Cart button and see what's going to happen.
So it shows a push prior to cart and incremental cart length.
It calls these two mutations.
Why.
Because this is the first time we push a product to this cart.
I say like this specific product there are no products exist in our cart yet.
So this will be push prior to cart.
But if you click it again it will be incremental product quantity instead because the product already
existed in our cart and it will just add an incremental cart Lang will always be call.
So if you click this loop state and there is a cart here and there's only one product in a cart but
a quantity is two.
But what if you want to add another product let's go and click go truants and click Add to cart again
push it to cart because it's a new product.
And if we load the state again and close this and you can see there are two products in here and the
cart length is three because Kimo trains the quantity one while Harry Potter is two.
So let's try to increase one more and then let's load the stating in and a Lang will be four.
So now we can call this car object and we can map it to our cart view page.
So if you go to cart so now we can map all of this product to here and we can also change this zero
to the cart length.
I'll see you guys in the next video.