In order for us to map the state to our NAF bar here which is the cart length we need to at getters
in our index DOJ us file.
So let's go to our editor and you want to type here.
Export Carnes getters getters is to get the state.
That's all.
We just want to return to state a map that state corresponding component.
So we need to type for example since we want to get the Lambert car we type GET cart Lang and we pass
interstate and we just wanted to one thing return state DOT cart Lane.
That's all we want.
We just want the value of cart length.
So if we go to nav bar under components and you want to go down you want to type import.
Since we have to map the getters to our cart component we have to map getters from view x.
But how do we map these getters.
Do we have to put it in methods because method is only for actions.
But do we put get map getters to data.
We are not going to map getters.
This doesn't work this way.
We have to use computed properties to actually map the getters so that we can use GET cart length.
So you must be wondering what is computed computed property.
Allow us to define a property which is something like get cart length to use the same way as data which
is it is the same thing as data actually but all the difference is is in computed.
We can add some custom logic.
So for example in data when we return it's gonna be like name and then we can do any computation here
or we can do any like custom logic in this name property.
But in it you can do name but you have to make it as a function and you have to return and then you
can do any logic you want you can see Jack plus one plus Sparrow so we can use this name property under
computed and then we can just simply put it here and then we can just put it like name super simple
so remember you only want to use compute it if you want to do some logic or you want to do some custom
logic in it like any logic they could think off then you can use compute it.
We never used computer before except right now because we need to map the getters you know compute it
this is the convention where you cannot map getters to data so you can only map getters to compute it
hence why we have to use compute it.
But in a future in index the jazz under these getters we're going to have some getter function that
will do some computation kind of make sense to map it to compute it.
So right now let's remove this and let's remove this and now we can pass this get cart Lang and we can
find a cart which is will be next thing to cart and then this will be get cart length.
Simple as that.
It will just return the length of the cart from the state.
So if we go back and go back to our main page and let's add some product into our cart so let's at Harry
Potter and I simply click Add to Cart and you can see it increase the cart length is now is three four
five and if you go back to inspect and check our view def tools and you can see if you look the state
and now we have one object which is one product and but the quantity is five which is correct.
So we have successfully map the state to the corresponding components in a next video we are going to
go to cart and we're going to map the cart data to the shopping cart.
So I'll see you guys in the next video.