In this video we are going to map the cart object into view X and we're going to map it till a shopping
cart full.
Go ahead and do that to go to you enter and you want to go to cart that view and down here you want
to type scrip and then you want to import get her map from view X but we haven't created the gather
for getting this cart seat.
So we have to go the index of yes.
And you want to type GET cart past the state and then we'll be return state DOT cart.
Simple as that.
And then now we can go back to cart a view and then we can create computed properties and then we can
type.
Dot dot dot which is spread operator map getters and more call GET cart.
You can copy get a cart and find lists of the item which is this part.
And now here you want to V for product in get cart past a key should be product dot undescribed D.
And move and map all the data here.
So product will be in here will be S or C should be colon.
And then product Dot photo.
Now we have product title we change this to product
and then as we Product Owner so does we product dot owner name.
And I would go down quantity.
This will handle this section later on that product price which will be product that price
and that's all you want to save it.
You want to go back and there we have it all the products we add.
So let's say we add a new product let's say we add another product would you be game of truant.
So if you add and add to cart and go back to a cart there would have to have two products in here.
But now we have to fix our price because the price is not thirty nine.
Price plus to be 29 times the quantity of the product.
Speaker to go back and we get a good price that's fine.
Price though we'll do a little bit of computation and we shall be program price times product dot quantity
save it and they we have it 1 9 5 which is correct because if you multiply twenty nine times five it
will be 1 9 5.
Now we haven't figure out how to accumulate the total price.
So how do we do this.
So let's go back to our index Rojas file and then we have to type get cart.
Total price pass in the state here and even a top let total equal to zero.
We just want to compute all of the prices you know cart.
So if you compute one and five plus eighty nine it will be 2 8 4.
So we won that total price so let's go back and let's do state DOT cart dot map.
So we want to loop all the product end product and and we want it to total plus equals the product price
and then we have to multiply it with product dot quantity and after that you want to return the total
because we have to return it.
Now let's go back to World card the view let's go down and let's put here.
Get card.
Total price.
Let's see the name.
It is the same.
All right let's go back.
And now we can call this get card.
Total price getter.
And then we can set it to our total price.
We should be card into the price.
And then we can change this to get caught.
Total price.
So if we go back it will be two it four which is correct.
And I want to change this ninety nine to 2 8 4 as well so as find that sum total three are and then
get a card total price and it will be to it for as well.
And they want to change the subtotal to item to the total product in our card which is six.
So let's go back to our Ed and you want to go down and you want to call one more thing which is get
cart length and copy this.
You want to find up to introduce to get cart length and let's find another subtotal.
Save it.
Let's go back.
Now we have supper all six items it goes to here as well.
So now if you refresh the page the whole product in the cart will disappear.
This is not the correct behavior that we won for our shopping cart feature.
We want the data to persist.
We're going to fix this in the next video.