Let's add a couple of products to our cart.
Go to Amazon homepage and let's go to Harry Potter.
Add to Cart and then if refresh it will disappear.
There is a way to fix that problem but before that we need to fix one single problem before we meet
our view X persisted.
So let's add the Harry Potter product I want to show you the book right now at the quantity increases.
But if we go back to Amazon if we go back to Harry Potter and try to add you can see that it shows not
a number because it's updating the new product quantity not the old product.
So in order for us to fix that we have to go back to View studio put index Rojas.
And you want to go to add product to cart and then in this L statement it has to be cart product or
else the quantity will be undefined.
And if we saved is go back and refresh and add to cart it shows for.
So if you go back to homepage and we go back to Harry Potter and then now if you click Add to Cart then
it will update the quantity of the product in the cart instead.
So now let's go to our cart and now our goal is to make this product persisted so that when we refresh
the page it will still stay there.
So to do that we have to go back to our editor.
And then you want to cancel your client and then you went to npm install you X persisted state dash
chief and then you want to go to plug ins this will first time creating a plug in file so new file and
name it local storage ideas and then you want to type import create persistent state from view X persistent
state and export default.
Now you add store and your window on NOx ready callback function here and then create persistence date
and an empty bracket in here and then we want to pass the store here
closes down so this library will store the view x state like cart or cart land into the local storage
or cookies so that when we have fresh the page the view X will grab the cart and cart Lang from local
storage or cookies and store it into view X once again.
So what is going on here.
First important to create persistent state it is a function that has been created by view X persistent
state library.
And then when NOx is ready you in the next app is ready.
We want to pass that store to our cookies or local storage so that it can map the local storage or cookies
back to our store.
So it is just utilizing the local storage or the cookies.
That's all there is nothing special about it.
And last thing we want to do is want to go to next conflict.
Yes.
And we have two important plugins.
So by adding a plug in as you can read here plugins will load before mounting the application when the
app was about to mount.
Then it will run that specific function which is great persistent state and then it will actually map
the local storage value or cookies to our view store.
So now we want to add a plug in in here which will be SLC then plug ins then that name or file that
we just created which would be storage local storage that yes and then we would add SS are false and
let's save this and let's go back to our beach and let's refresh the speech.
Oh sorry I need to we need to start a server back which run port nine thousand NPM run death so let's
go back and let's try to refresh this speech.
Let's tried to add a couple of products
or add this and let's try another product.
You'll be given a truant cart and try to refreshed it
and it can see the data persisted because we have upgraded our view X to work together with local storage
and cookies.
This library is amazing.
Or else we have to manually map the view X to local storage and cookies.
So we go to application and let's check local store it is going to see if you click view X and if you
go down here we make it bigger and you can see that as a cart.
State of state and cart Lang state you can ignore off because of it's already been persistent before
by the library.
But we're going to focus on car and cart length which we persisted in the local storage and it did not
save in cookies it just save in local storage.
So there's no VFX here so it's only save in local storage.
So right now we don't have the ability to change the quantity of our product and or delete the product
in the next video we will implement the change quantity feature so that user can change the quantity
of the product.
I'll see you guys in the next video.