In this video we will add a change quantity features so the user can change the quantity of the product.
Let's add to our index DOJ as in creating a new mutation function.
So go here and you want to go to Index project and scroll down to your mutations and we want to add
a new mutation function which will be change quantity and if we want to add the note up here of what
is the algorithm.
So the first step is to find the product in the car.
And then second is to change the quantity of the product.
Once we have found the protein core and then we want to update the length of the cart and finally we
want to replace the old product with the updated product.
So let's write down in change quantity you want to pass in state and then product and then the quantity
we're going to get this quantity from the front end.
So let's find the product in the cart first go to state DOT cart not find an import product and describe
the equivalent to product.
I do.
And then after that we want to cart product dot quantity equals to quantity
so it should be first step second step.
And now is the third step is to update the length of the cart so we can just copy this and it's not
a good idea to actually copy the same thing that have been written over and over again.
But we just want to test it first.
Then only we can refactor this and put it in a separate function.
And last thing we want to replace the old product with the updated product.
So let index of product equals to state that cart the index off cart product.
And we're going to get the index of the product in the cart and then you want to do splice so we can
replace the old product with the updated product so state that cart does splice an index of product
that we want to pass in the cart product.
So now we can call this you know a front end which is in cart of you pitch.
So now let's head back to a cart of you and you want to find a select which is the quantity select and
the first thing we want is we want to loop this so that we'll have more than one quantity so we can
choose 1 2 or 3 and 4 before I in list keep it maximum 10 key will be I.
And then the value will be I.
And then this will be save this let's go back to our chrome check the quantity.
Then now we have more than one quantity we can choose 1 2 3 4 5 6.
Until then and then let's go back and let's implement a function where we can actually call the mutation
function.
So you want to add methods here and then on change quantity
now you pass an event and product.
And they wanted to let equals to quantity equals event not target not value.
So by doing event on target of value we can access the value of the option which will be if you go back
to select we can access the value of the specific option tap.
So now we want to do this.
That store
change quantity and we passing product in as well as the quantity.
So we can actually call the REC lead mutation function the reason why I don't want to put it in action
because it's just one line.
So I think it's better because it is directly called the mutation function here.
And let's call this unchanged quantity you know select in select.
You want to do at change because you on change quantity and then you have to pass in the event parameter
and the product to save this and let's go and test it up let's go to Google Chrome refresh this page
and you can open up your view death to so that we can see the changes to state and then let's change
this quantity to five.
And it did change the price and as well as the total price.
But we have a problem.
If you can see the cart it shows 0 5 2.
Why is that.
If you go back to our Ed to data type for this value is actually the not a number is a string.
So to fix that you want to go here and we want to convert the string to I.A..
So the best way to do that is to type pass a..
So that you will convert the string into number because when string and numbers are added together it
will become a string.
That's why it shows 0 5 2.
So as safeties and let's test it again So refresh and it can see it's still 0 5 2.
So we have to go to our application we have to remove the view X and we have to go back to Amazon and
refresh first.
And I want to click Harry Potter add to cart.
Let's go back here and click get more troops to CAR again.
Let's go back here and we change this to seven.
Now it worked because now it is not a string anymore it is.
It is a number.
So this is really amazing because if you change this quantity now the price will change in even a total
price.
And even though cart Lang as well.
But if we refresh the page this quantity will be back to one and one.
So how do we make it to the original quantity.
So let's go and to select.
We have to add a selected value here.
And for us to do that we need to create a small method which would be check quantity and product quantity
and the quantity that we got from the option.
And if we want to pass both of this equals to pass I.A. and even a quantity we want to pass return true
else.
We want to return false safeties and copiers and go back to shellac and let's pass the function here
and then pass in the product quantity and as well as the value I safeties and let's refresh the speech
and I can see now it shows the quantity that we chose so let's change it to seven.
And if you refresh it will be seven.
We have completed our quantity feature in this video.
So in the next video we will add the ability for the user to delete one of the products in the cart.
I'll see you guys in the next video.