In this video we will add the ability for the user to delete one of the products in the cart.
Let's go to our index DOJ s and we have to add another mutation function which will be removed.
Product let's write the algorithm up here and the algorithm is remove the product quantity from the
cart length and then the second one is get the index of the product that we want to delete.
And the final one is remove that product by using splice and in the parameter you want to pass in the
state and then a product.
And the first we need to remove the products quantity from the cart length.
So do state that cart length minus product quantity.
After that we want to get the index of a product that we wanted to lead.
So let index off product it goes to state the card not index of an end product.
Finally we want to remove that product by using this place.
So state DOT card dots place as in the index of the product.
And then we just want to remove one element from the car every.
So now we have to call this you know a cart to go to cart a view and that's fine.
Delete button we can directly call it here.
So at click would you be store
and then the name of the mutation would be removed.
Product and we simply have to pass in the product in save it and we have to make it single quote or
else we wouldn't work
because it's already double quote.
So we need to make it single couldn't say who saved is and let's go back to a cart strike to refresh
it first and let's remove one of products remove Harry Potter and there we have it.
It removes the product and even it removes the product quantity from cart length.
And now the total price is 6 to 3 which is correct can play around with it.
We can change and if we refresh a report that won't be there anymore and we have it now we have implemented
the Add to Cart feature it is working correctly and in the next feed you will implement the payment
system so we can buy all the products.
I'll see you guys in the next video.